Team GoUNC


I feel soon I will sink into you
What do you think?
'Cause there's still blood in your hair
Got the bruise of the year


But there's something about her long, shady eyes
I'm all about her shade tonight


I hate your tattoos
You have weak wrists
But I'll keep you


'Cause there's something about her long, shady eyes
I'm all about her shade tonight

Well, it's too bad
It's too bad
It's too bad
You're married to me


Team GoUNC